

linkedin.com/in/aaron-bruno

aaronbruno.github.io/aaronbruno

### **PROFILE**

Level Designer with over 4+ years' experience in creating games in team sizes ranging from 1 to 10+ teammates. Published several games with a recent launch of BALLISTIC on Steam where I led a team of 11 over a 6 month period as the Production Lead and Level/Technical Designer. 3+ years work experience in leading and managing teams of 20+ people in high intensity environments. Looking to bring my skills and start my career in the game industry.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **B.S.** in Computer Science: Game Design

University of California, Santa Cruz

• Related Coursework: Game Design Studio, Game Production Studio, Game AI, Game Technologies

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Group Tutor - Foundations of Video Game Design, University of California, Santa Cruz

Jan 2024 - April 2024

Sep 2020 - June 2024

- Collaborated with teaching staff to enhance student learning experiences
- Facilitated discussion sections to support students' understanding of course material
- Provided personalized assistance through tutoring sessions for code debugging, playtesting or Q/A

## Student Supervisor - Dining Hall, University of California, Santa Cruz

Jan 2023 - Jan 2024

- Worked closely with management and staff to improve the dining hall's customer and worker satisfaction
- Managed teams of 20+ dining hall student workers to ensure quality and efficient service throughout the dining hall
- Completed adminstrative tasks such as reviewing and submitting timesheets for over 200 dining hall student workers

### Food Service Worker - Dining Hall, University of California, Santa Cruz

Aug 2021 - Jan 2023

- Provided a welcoming dining experience and exceptional customer service
- Interacted with customers and resolved customer complaints in a friendly and helpful manner
- Accurately and efficiently performed various tasks such as handling food, processing financial transactions and cleaning

#### **NOTABLE PROJECTS**

### **BALLISTIC - Production Lead & Level+Technical Designer**

Jan 2024 - Present

- Led a team of 11, during a 6 month period, in the creation and publishing of BALLISTIC, an online multiplayer dodgeball game (made with Unity, <u>available on Steam</u>)
- Facilitated team meetings, oversaw production timelines, and utilized Miro to increase productivity and organization
- Designed and implemented 5 unique maps while assisting in implementing 5 other maps (learn more here)

#### Witch Craft - Character/Enemy Artist & Map Designer

Nov 2023 - Dec 2023

- Collaborated with 2 others, during a 3 week period, in the creation and launch of Witch Craft, a singeplayer magic shooter roque-lite with crafting elements (made with Unity, available on Itch.io)
- Created the main menu map + UI. Features a variety of lighting, SFX, and VFX to create an immersive main menu
- Modeled, textured and animated the character and enemies using Blender in a low-poly art style

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Game Engines & Tools: Unity, Unreal Engine, Blender, Autodesk Maya, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Git, VS Code Scripting & Programming: C#, C++, C, Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS Miscellaneous: Miro, Trello, Slack, Figma, Google Suite